Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 9.25; (3 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  - Box 19, folder 396 (Box 76, Folder 1035)
  - Box 19, folder 407 (Box 76, Folder 1036)
  - Box 19, folder 414 (Box 76, Folder 1037)
  - Box 20, folder 420 (Box 76, Folder 1038)
  - Box 20, folder 428 (Box 76, Folder 1039)
  - Box 21, folder 457 (Box 76, Folder 1040)
  - Box 21, folder 466 (Box 76, Folder 1041)
  - Box 28, folder 550 (Box 76, Folder 1042)
  - Box 19, folder 409 (Box bsd, folder 1043)
- Restricted Material, 0.21; (1 box)
  Restricted Material consists of Series X, Assassination Plot and box 55. For further information, consult the appropriate curator.
  - Description of restricted audiotapes originally in Levy inventory, [1998] (Box 77, Folder 1044)
- CD-ROM Reference Copies of Audiotapes, 10; (20 boxes)
  CD-ROM Reference Copies of Audiotapes contains the box listing for reference copies from Series I, II, VI, VII and X, and is in order.
  - Folders 1-16 (Box 78)
  - Folders 17-30 (Box 79)
  - Folders 31-46 (Box 80)
  - Folders 47-60 (Box 81)
  - Folders 61-76 (Box 82)
  - Folders 77-91 (Box 83)
  - Folders 92-105 (Box 84)
  - Folders 106-121 (Box 85)
  - Folders 122-128, 208-221 (Box 86)
  - Folders 222-240 (Box 87)
  - Folders 241-255d (Box 88)
  - Folders 255e-255i, 517-527 (Box 89)
  - Folders 528-533, 599-608 (Box 90)
  - Folders 609-622 (Box 91)
  - Folders 623-636 (Box 92)
  - Folders 637-654 (Box 93)
  - Folders 655-669 (Box 94)
  - Folders 670-671 (Box 95)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIAL
    - Folders 827-846, 855 (Box 96)
    - Folders 856-865 (Box 97)
- August 2007 Acquisition, 1966-1978; 0.91; (3 boxes)
  Consists of contact sheets of photographs by Jacques Levy, all apparently from March of 1977, notes, ephemera, and memorabilia relating to Cesar Chavez's trip to Europe in 1974, and printed material relating to Chavez and the Farmworkers Union.
  - Contact sheets, 1977 March; 18 folders
  - Trip to Europe, 1974; 3 folders
  - Trip to Europe, 1974; 3 folders
  - Printed material, 1966-1975; 6 folders
  - Printed material, 1972-1974; 2 folders